Contact

Syria - Damascus +963962020543 (Mobile) hadi90abo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hadi-aboesha (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

English Teaching Writing **Educational Assessment**

Languages

Arabic (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Start - up Business

IELTS Speaking - Teacher Training Program – Understanding the IELTS Assessment Criteria - 2021

Teach English Now! Second Language Listening, Speaking, and Pronunciation

Interpreter Or Translator

Honors-Awards

Appreciation Certificate

Hadi Aboesha

ESL | EFL | ELT Instructor | "Experienced and Passionate ESL Instructor | Empowering Multicultural Communication & Language Fluency | Proven Track Record of Success in Guiding Diverse Learners to Excellence"

Damascus, Damascus Governorate, Syria

Summary

A qualified teacher by the University of Arizona I also have a Bachelor's in Translation as well as I am seeking to gain my master's in Education at the University of the People in advanced teaching This means I can help you with any language needs you might have

I have over five years of tutoring experience teaching English to both groups and individuals face-to-face, online

I have taught students from different levels starting from the beginner to the advanced level

Teaching is all about people and I've always been a very approachable and supportive educator

As a language learner myself I am familiar with the struggles and frustration that students may encounter when learning a language, and I am passionate about English and I always try to infuse my lesson with interesting material and make them more memorable Over the year of teaching, I've helped students pass the exams and improve their general level of English

Get the job of their dreams and gain more confidence when they speak

I teach different courses such as

The conversational course where you can practice your speaking and gain more confidence when speaking to foreigners

General English where you can practice all four language skills writing listening reading and speaking

English for starters from 1st to 12th grades

Job interviews, business meetings, public presentations

Where you can build your confidence when applying for a job abroad

I have great cultural awareness as I read more and more about differentiation among them.

As well as these I am a former Human Skills Developer and motivational speaker in both Arabic and English which means that I can create a very entertaining atmosphere.

And I also have an experience in HR consultation that allows me to give many job interviews recommendations, especially with a high level of self-esteem

I can help you with English for the workplace Moreover, I am very good at catering my lessons to meet your needsCourses

Experience

Pakistan International School of Damascus English Language Teacher January 2023 - Present (8 months) Damascus, Damascus Governorate, Syria

Junior English instructor.

Islamic Studies English instructor.

Cambridge IGCSE English - First Language

Syllabus overview

Cambridge IGCSE First Language English is designed for learners whose first language is English. The course enables learners to:

- -develop the ability to communicate clearly, accurately and effectively when speaking and writing
- -use a wide range of vocabulary, and the correct grammar, spelling and punctuation

develop a personal style and an awareness of the audience being addressed.

Private Tutor & English Teacher (University Level) Freelance English Language Teacher

March 2020 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- -Online tutoring and giving English Courses for Engineers
- Preparing them for IELTS test.
- Encourage them to take a new Step and begin the Conversation.
- Use 80/20 and other Strategies to Rev up their levels

BeFluent

English Second Language Teacher

August 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Damascus, Syria

(Interchange, Intro, 1.A levels, Cambridge University)

- Helping students pass the exams improve their general level of English
- -Get the job of their dreams and gain more confidence when they speak
- -Giving them a chance to make a General English challenges that they might face through the Speaking

GLOBAL LANGUAGE TRANSLATION SERVICES LTD.

English Second Language Instructor October 2021 - October 2022 (1 year 1 month) Syria

(Speak out, Starter, Elementary, intermediate, upper intermediate, Oxford University)

- .prepare the suitable strategies for the participants
- . work on the main skills into the class
- . increase the knowledge capacity by using interactive exercises
- . follow up the modern technologies and relate it with the classroom activities
- . correct the common misunderstanding linguistics an terminological issues

Nour Foundation for Relief and Development English Second Language Instructor July 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 4 months) Syria

(Headway Beginner, Elementary levels)

- . Working on the main skills of English Language as a Foreign language.
- . Motivate Women to create a new life after starting and mastering the language.
- . Engage the participants with the social by making tours around the famous places and let the try to describe these things and places.
- . Focusing on their abilities of Speaking, Writing to get them into job market.

Jafra Foundation English Second Language Instructor September 2018 - April 2019 (8 months) Syria

UNICEF

English Language Instructor May 2013 - September 2013 (5 months)

Damascus, Syria

- Helping students pass the exams improve their general level of English
- -Get the job of their dreams and gain more confidence when they speak

UNRWA

English club leader

March 2012 - August 2013 (1 year 6 months)

Damascus, Damascus Governorate, Syria

The first step in the world of teaching English.

A very humble beginning in the journey of training and teaching English.

Education

University of the People

Master of Education - MEd, Special Education and Teaching (2022 - 2024)

Damascus University

Bachelor, English Language and Literature/Letters · (July 2010 - January 2014)

Arizona State University

TESOL, Teaching English as a Second or Foreign Language/ESL Language Instructor · (August 2023)